<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>nagabonor@denny</title>
    <link>www.dennysinaga.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on nagabonor@denny</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 19:50:12 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="www.dennysinaga.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>[CTF] Pointer Overflow CTF 2023</title>
      <link>www.dennysinaga.com/blog/pointer-overflow-ctf-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 19:50:12 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>www.dennysinaga.com/blog/pointer-overflow-ctf-2023/</guid>
      <description>UWSP Pointer Overflow CTF Crack The Gentle Rocking of the Sun  Here&amp;rsquo;s a password protected archive. Problem is that I seem to have forgotten das Passwort. All I have is this post-it note on my monitor that says &amp;ldquo;crack2 = 4bd939ed2e01ed1e8540ed137763d73cd8590323&amp;rdquo;
 In this challenge, we were provided with a crack2.7z file. You can download it here.
To solve this challenge, we should find the password of this archive file.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[CTF - Lokal] CTF SecureTheSystem 2023</title>
      <link>www.dennysinaga.com/blog/ctf-securethesystem-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 14:28:17 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>www.dennysinaga.com/blog/ctf-securethesystem-2023/</guid>
      <description>CTF Secur{i}e The System 2023 This post will be written in Bahasa Indonesia.
Forensic keylogger  So, here&amp;rsquo;s the thing. I just came to the Internet caffee (warnet) and after several minutes using the computer, I found a strange process running in the backround. Then i found out it was a keylogger. Luckily I can stop the process and don&amp;rsquo;t let the attacker get this keylogger file. Because i just logged in to my server before.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[CTF] The Cyber Cooperative CTF 2023</title>
      <link>www.dennysinaga.com/blog/the-cybercooperative-ctf-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 11:34:01 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>www.dennysinaga.com/blog/the-cybercooperative-ctf-2023/</guid>
      <description>The Cyber Cooperative CTF 2023 Link: CTFtime.org
reversing bunker  You reach a large metal door. It&amp;rsquo;s protected by large yellow bars. There appears to be an panel with a keypad&amp;hellip;
 In this challenge, we were provided with the Bunker.jar file. To open this file, I utilized jadx-gui.
package defpackage; import java.awt.Component; import java.awt.event.ActionEvent; import java.awt.event.ActionListener; import javax.swing.JButton; import javax.swing.JFrame; import javax.swing.JOptionPane; import javax.swing.JPanel; import javax.swing.JTextField; import javax.swing.UIManager; /* compiled from: bunker.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[CTF] PatriotCTF 2023</title>
      <link>www.dennysinaga.com/blog/patriot-ctf-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 09:45:04 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>www.dennysinaga.com/blog/patriot-ctf-2023/</guid>
      <description>PatriotCTF - 2023 Link: CTFtime.org
Crypto Multi-numeral You are given a text file containing binary strings. You can use CyberChef to decode the strings:
flag: PCTF{w0w_s0_m4ny_number5}
My phone! We were provided with an image file that appeared to contain an unusual cipher. To decrypt the message within the image, I utilized the Gravity Falls Bill Cipher tool.
By decoding the message from the image, I obtained a result like this:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>$whoami</title>
      <link>www.dennysinaga.com/whoami/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 20:27:33 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>www.dennysinaga.com/whoami/</guid>
      <description>Hello everyone! I&amp;rsquo;m Denny Abraham Sinaga, a recent graduate from Del Institute of Technology. During university, I worked as a Penetration Tester, diving into cybersecurity. In 2023, I embarked on Capture The Flag (CTF) adventures, earning a CEH certification this year, solidifying my commitment to cybersecurity.
Looking ahead, I&amp;rsquo;m gearing up for new cybersecurity adventures. If only opportunities were as abundant as cat videos online! Ideally, I&amp;rsquo;d expand my knowledge, skills, and maybe stumble upon a career-defining moment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Draft</title>
      <link>www.dennysinaga.com/achievement/draft/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 11:53:31 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>www.dennysinaga.com/achievement/draft/</guid>
      <description>This is test page.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
